Luke Thomson Technical Artist

contact@floofinator.com

Please ask for Address Please ask for Phone Number

SUMMARY

As a technical artist, I focus on creative production through technical understanding. My goal is to use technology and the functionality it allows to create experiences for others to be entertained by. My focus is on the creation of entertainment through computer programming, graphics, and animation.

EDUCATION

Florida Polytechnic University

Graduated April 2024

Lakeland, Florida

Bachelor's in Computer Science, Game Development and Simulation

KEY SKILLS

Programming Languages - C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, Python, Lua, GDScript

Management - Git, GitHub, Team Organization, Design Documentation

Graphics Programming - HLSL, GLSL, Visual Shader Graph

3D Modelling, Texturing, Rigging, Animation - Blender, Maya

2D Art and Animation - Clip Studio Paint, Krita, Photoshop

Web Development - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST, APIs, Node.js, React.js, Vue.js

HOBBIES

Drawing, Character Design, Environment Design, Story Writing, Game Design.

EXPERIENCE

Technical Artist - Dream BBQ

Joel G EIRL - Remote

April 2022 - 2024

Remote work on the ENA series game Dream BBQ.

3D Animation

Asset Integration

VFX development

Club Vice President

Florida Poly Media Club - Lakeland, FL

2021 - 2022

Managed club budget and purchase requests for events.

Organized Florida Poly Respawn Game Jam and Game Expo.

PROJECTS

GMTK Game Jam

2019 - 2020 - 2021 - 2022

Created multiple game prototypes around a theme in only 48 hours.

Planned and organized tasks independently to manage scope and resources.

Personal Game Projects

Developed and released multiple game projects to Itch.io.

https://floofinator.itch.io/

Created and hosted a personal website.

https://floofinator.com/

2nd Place Undergraduate FIEA Statewide Game Jam

FIEA - Orlando, FL

January 2024

Developed a game in a team of 4 in under 48 hours.

Developed concept and design by team brainstorming.

Acknowledged limitations and manageable scope.

Modeled 3D assets while integrating textures from 2D artist.

Created Animation and programmed visuals.

Communicated goals and necessary tasks with the team to ensure work was formed into a viable product by the deadline.

https://fiea.ucf.edu/news/fiea-and-florida-polytechnic-students-win-fieas-first-game-jam/